https://www.novaconcerts.com/privacypolicy.html

Mail via Website
On Tour:
Kyle Eastwood
Bassist Kyle Eastwood is an outstanding performer and bandleader whose sound straddles the line between straight-ahead acoustic post-bop and contemporary jazz. In Co-Operation with V.O MUSIC / France
Available / On Tour:
March, April, May, June, July, August 2021
Kenny Garrett
Grammy award winning saxophonist Kenny Garrett is a true virtuoso on the saxophone and is considered to be the 'most important alto saxophonist of his generation' (Washington City Paper). In conjunction with Nathan Horne.
Available / On Tour:
July, October, November 2020, May 2021
Steve Harley Acoustic Band
Steve Harley celebrates his 47th year in music in 2020 and continues to play concerts around the world. He says that playing 'live' is more than a job, it’s almost his life’s blood.
Available / On Tour:
Generally available 2020 & 2021
Datenschutzerklärung:
Privacy Policy
Thank you for visiting our website and your interest in our services and products. As the protection of your personal data is an important concern for us, we will explain below what information we collect during your visit to our website, as they are processed and whether or how these may be used.
Wir bedanken uns für Ihren Besuch auf unserer Webseite sowie über Ihr Interesse an unseren Dienstleistungen und Produkten. Da der Schutz Ihrer personenbezogenen Daten für uns ein wichtiges Anliegen ist, erläutern wir Ihnen im Folgenden, welche Informationen wir während Ihres Besuches auf unserer Webseite erfassen, wie diese verarbeitet und ob beziehungsweise wie diese weiter genutzt werden.
Personal data / Personenbezogene Daten
Personal information is information about personal or material circumstances of an identified or identifiable natural person. This includes information such as your first and last name, your postal or residential address, telephone numbers and date of birth. Information that can not be directly related to your real identity - such as your favorite websites or the number of users of a page - are not considered as personal data.
Personenbezogene Daten sind Einzelangaben über persönliche oder sachliche Verhältnisse einer bestimmten oder bestimmbaren natürlichen Person. Darunter fallen Informationen wie zum Beispiel Ihr Vor- und Zuname, Ihre Post- oder Wohnanschrift, Ihre Telefonnummern und Ihr Geburtsdatum. Informationen, die nicht direkt mit Ihrer wirklichen Identität in Verbindung gebracht werden können - wie zum Beispiel Ihre favorisierten Webseiten oder die Anzahl der Nutzer einer Seite - sind keine personenbezogenen Daten.
Collection and processing of personal data / Erhebung und Verarbeitung von personenbezogenen Daten
As the operator and creator of the website, we do not store personal data itself automatically. If you go to our website, the provider - where the web server is hosted - may temporarily store data for the purpose of system security such as the connection of the computer, the web pages you visit, the date and duration of the visit, data about the used browser software and operating system and the web page from which you visit us. In addition to that, personal information such as your name, address, phone number or e-mail will only be stored, if you have provided this information voluntarily, eg. when using our online booking forms (Booking Enquiries), when subscribing to our newsletter (Newsletter Service) or getting in contact with us via email or the contact form on this website (Mail via Website).
Als Betreiber und Ersteller des Webauftrittes speichern wir selbst keine personenbezogenen Daten automatisch ab. Wenn Sie aber unsere Webseiten besuchen, speichern die Provider - dort, wo der Webserver gehostet wird - standardmäßig zum Zweck der Systemsicherheit temporär die Verbindungsdaten des anfragenden Rechners, die Webseiten, die Sie bei uns besuchen, das Datum und die Dauer des Besuches, die Erkennungsdaten des verwendeten Browser- und Betriebssystem-Typs sowie die Webseite, von der aus Sie uns besuchen. Darüber hinaus gehend werden personenbezogene Angaben wie Ihr Name, Ihre Anschrift, Telefonnummer oder E-Mail-Adresse nur erfasst, wenn Sie diese Angaben freiwillig gemacht haben, zum Beispiel wenn sie die Anfragen über Online-Buchungsformulare (Booking Enquiries) vornehmen, wenn Sie sich in unserem Newsletterverteiler eintragen (Newsletter Service) oder wenn Sie mit uns per Email oder über das Kontaktformular dieser Webseite (Mail via Website) mit uns in Verbindung treten.
Use and disclosure of personal data / Nutzung und Weitergabe der personenbezogenen Daten
Personal data you provided may be used solely for the purpose of technical website administration and to fulfill your wishes and requirements, thus primarily to processing the order with you or to respond to your request. We don't share, sell or transfer your personal data to third parties, unless this is necessary for the purpose of the contract or unless you have explicitly consented.
Die von Ihnen zur Verfügung gestellten personenbezogenen Daten verwenden wir ausschließlich zum Zweck der technischen Administration der Webseiten und zur Erfüllung Ihrer Wünsche und Anforderungen, also in der Regel zur Abwicklung des mit Ihnen geschlossenen Vertrages oder zur Beantwortung Ihrer Anfrage. Eine Weitergabe, Verkauf oder sonstige Übermittlung Ihrer personenbezogenen Daten an Dritte erfolgt nicht, es sei denn, dass dies zum Zwecke der Vertragsabwicklung erforderlich ist oder Sie ausdrücklich eingewilligt haben.
Security / Sicherheit
We take all the necessary technical and organisational security measures to protect your personal data from loss and misuse. Your data is stored in a secure operating environment that is not accessible to the public. If you communicate with us via e-mail, please note that the confidentiality of the information is not guaranteed. The contents of e-mails can be intercepted by third parties. In case of doubt we therefore recommend to send confidential information only by mail.
Wir treffen alle notwendigen technischen und organisatorischen Sicherheitsmaßnahmen, um Ihre personenbezogenen Daten vor Verlust und Missbrauch zu schützen. So werden Ihre Daten in einer sicheren Betriebsumgebung gespeichert, die der Öffentlichkeit nicht zugänglich ist. Sollten Sie mit uns per E-Mail in Kontakt treten wollen, weisen wir darauf hin, dass die Vertraulichkeit der übermittelten Informationen nicht gewährleistet ist. Der Inhalt von E-Mails kann von Dritten eingesehen werden. Wir empfehlen Ihnen daher im Zweifelsfall vertrauliche Informationen ausschließlich über den Postweg zu versenden.
Right of access to personal data / Auskunftsrecht
Upon written request you will be informed by us what information we stored about you (such as name or address).
Auf schriftliche Anfrage werden Sie von uns darüber informiert, welche Daten wir über Ihre Person (zum Beispiel Name oder Adresse) gespeichert haben.
Contact / Kontakt
If you have questions regarding the processing of personal data or in case of requests for information, suggestions or complaints, please contact directly support@novaconcerts.com.
Wenn Sie Fragen hinsichtlich der Verarbeitung Ihrer persönlichen Daten haben, wenden Sie sich bitte an support@novaconcerts.com. Auch im Falle von Auskunftsersuchen, Anregungen oder Beschwerden stehen wir Ihnen zur Verfügung.
This privacy policy statement is based on a comparable policy statement at www.libreoffice.org. Like the original, the text of this policy statement is licensed under the Creative Commons Attribution-Share Alike 3.0 License.
Artist Profiles
Ola Onabulé
Kyle Eastwood
Kenny Garrett
Steve Harley Acoustic Band
Jean Luc Ponty
Michel Camilo & Tomatito
Bob Geldof
© 2020 Nova Concerts International - Website Version 4.36 - Legal Info - Privacy Policy - Last page update: Oct/07/2020 - Valid HTML5
